nettv4u.com 2017-12-01

# Read our Privacy Policy

(“Nettv4u”, “we”, “our”, “us”) is dedicated in delivering the safest and extremely secure environment for all its users. We are also committed in protecting the user’s privacy and handling personal information with supervision and respect. Nettv4u furnished this Privacy Policy Statement to assist the users in making a knowledgeable decision on whether to use or discontinue using this website. This Privacy Policy explains how Nettv4u and its contributors consider the user’s personal information when using the Nettv4u website and services. This Privacy Policy will notify the users regarding our policies and procedures on using our website and protecting all the information concerning our services.

This Privacy Policy is integrated and subject to our Terms and Conditions.

## The Information that we collect from our users:

Nettv4u is dedicated to protecting the user’s privacy and data information. The information that we collect on our users while using the Nettv4u website are the following:

  1. Like any other websites, Nettv4u may place cookies to your computer’s hard drive. We may transfer cookies to your computer if your browser is established to accept cookies. This is a diminutive piece of data with a string of alphanumeric characters that distinctively identifies your web browser so you can easily load Nettv4u the next time you visit our site. Nettv4u will use session cookies and persistent cookies. The Session Cookie is provisional and it will disappear once you close your browser. You can set to refuse all cookies or denote when a cookie is being sent. But, some features of Nettv4u website may stop working correctly. The Persistent Cookie remains even when you already close your browser. Your browser may use this on your succeeding visits to the website. Nettv4u uses cookies to record the information so you never have to re-enter our site when you visit it again. The information that we stored are non-personally identifiable information. However, if you do not wish this information to be collected, you can normally opt out of providing this information by configuring your browser to disallow cookies. But please be reminded that some section of the Nettv4u website may not dispense reasonable user experience if you have turned off the use of cookies. 
  2. We will be using third-party advertising companies to provide ads while you browse Nettv4u. The third-party advertisers and ad servers will put and display their ads on our site and they may also gather user information via cookies, pixel tag, clear GIF or Web Beacon and other similar methods. Third-party advertisers and ad servers may utilize the information they gathered for presenting their advertisements, for assessing and evaluating the efficiency of their advertisements, or other uses. The use and the gathered user’s information by the third-party advertisers and ad servers is administered by the significant privacy policy of the third-party and therefore, it is not covered by the Nettv4u Privacy Policy Statement. The privacy policy of Nettv4u is certainly distinct from the privacy policy of the third-party advertisers and ad servers.
  3. When using the Nettv4u website, our servers will automatically record specific information from your browser. Nettv4u collect server logs; including the Internet Protocol or IP address, web request, browser type and language, domain names, pages viewed, number of clicks, referring or exit pages, URLs, span of time that the user spent on particular pages, date and time of your request, platform type and cookies.
  4. When using the Nettv4u website, we may use Web Beacons, Web Bug, Pixel Tag or clear GIFs. This is used to supervise the user’s behavior while visiting our website. We will use this in monitoring the user’s online usage patterns anonymously.
  5. We utilize third-party analytics tools such as Google Analytics to assess the traffic and usage of our website. The analytic tools will gather information from your browser such as a web page request, web pages that you visit, height, width and add-ons of a browser, and other information that helps us in improving our service. We gather and utilize the following information in a collective form so it could not be manipulated to recognize a particular or individual user.
  6. Nettv4u does not use personally identifiable information to use our service. We do not require users to create an account to use our site. However, Nettv4u provides an option for our users to send their inquiries through our Contact Us form, which may require you to fill up the form with your name, email address and your personal message to us. Contact Us form will be used to provide our users a simpler way to reach us. It is our policy not to disclose your Name and E-mail Address publicly, nor use your e-mail address to send commercial, marketing, promotional offers or spam messages. However, we may utilize your email address without further consent to notify you for the upcoming major changes on Nettv4u website or anything that concerns only our service.

It is our policy to take necessary actions in accordance with the present legislation.

## Disqus Service:

Nettv4u uses the Disqus Service; a commenting platform that allows the users to make comments and discussions online. Nettv4u users should need to have their own Disqus account to participate or send their comments to the subject of our site. To create a Disqus account, you may need to go directly to [https://disqus.com](https://disqus.com/) and provide a username, password and an email address. In this case, Nettv4u is not responsible for all the information that you will provide in Disqus. We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information, and therefore, it is not covered by the Nettv4u Privacy Policy Statement. 

When using the Disqus public commenting platform on Nettv4u website, other users may search, use or re-post the content that you published through our site. Nettv4u cannot control the uses of the information that you voluntarily transmit online, and by using our service, you believe the possibility that the information you provided becomes publicly available and may be used, seen or viewed by other users and third-parties. Nettv4u will not be responsible for any unauthorized use of all the information you will provide in the Disqus platform. We cannot ensure or guarantee your security for the information you transmit to the Disqus platform. Nettv4u is not responsible for the functionality and security of any of the third-party services.

## Other Website Links:

Nettv4u is not responsible for the procedures used by websites linked to or its contents. Please be reminded that when you click a link to go from Nettv4u to another website, this Privacy Policy Statement is no longer in effect. Browsing and any communication to another website such as, those that contains a link to Nettv4u website, is subject to their own regulations.

Nettv4u is an online video indexing website and we do not upload or host any media files. All the videos posted on our website are transmitted on [www.youtube.com](http://www.youtube.com/), [www.dailymotion.com](http://www.dailymotion.com/) or similar websites. However, we are not responsible for any damages or breach in the terms of use of our sources. If you have any issues in the media content posted on our website, please contact the respected owners or website of those copyrighted media content. If by chance that Nettv4u posted any of your copyrighted material, please feel free to contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#52012722223d2026121c3726262466277c313d3f).

## How is this Collected Information used?

  1. We use your non-personally-identifiable information, like cookies, IP address, browser type, data usage and more for improving and developing the quality and the design of our website.
  2. And also, for creating the elements of the website, make new promotions and services by analyzing the user’s preferences.
  3. When using our website and submit personally identifiable information through our Contact Us form, we use this information to provide you an answer to all your queries or consider your comments and suggestions for maintaining and improving our website.
  4. Any personal information or links that you voluntarily disclose in Disqus commenting platform becomes available to the public and therefore, it can be seen and used by other users. We are not responsible for any unauthorized use of this information.
  5. Cookies, Web Beacons, server log details or log file information are used to remember information so you don’t need to re-enter the same site address the next time you visit the Nettv4u website and to monitor and track the number of visitors, how many times the website was viewed, and more.
  6. You may find links to other websites provided by other users through Disqus or access to the products and services offered by the third party advertisers and ad servers.

We do not provide any personally identifiable information to the third-party advertisers or ad servers without your consent or only if it’s a portion of a certain program on which you have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. But please be reminded that if an advertiser will ask our site to present an advertisement to a particular audience or audience segment, and you respond to it, the third-party advertiser or ad server may assume that you fitted to the description of the audience that they need. The third-party advertisers and ad servers may also use your information concerning your use of the Nettv4u website, like how many times you viewed an ad to find out which ads they will provide to you.

The use of the information you provided to those sites and services are being managed by the privacy policy of the owner or operator of the site you visited and therefore, we have no control of that. You may need to consult the privacy policies of those sites and third-party advertisers or ad servers for more information on their instructions and procedures on how to opt-in or opt-  
out some of their practices.

## Legitimacy of pulling content from our sources:

Our goal is to obtain and gather TV shows, TV serials, and short films in English and Indian languages like, Telegu, Tamil, Kannada and Hindi into one site and classify them based on all the rational information. Nettv4u will collect and re-use the copyright-protected materials from reputable sources such as [www.youtube.com](http://www.youtube.com/), [www.dailymotion.com](http://www.dailymotion.com/) and similar websites. Nettv4u uses the term “Fair use” or a legal policy stating that anyone can re-use or copy copyrighted materials in certain conditions (such as using for educational purposes) without needing to ask consent from the copyright owner. This process is a defense contrary to copyright infringement. We are pulling TV serials, TV shows and short films from our sources in a lawful manner.

## Security:

Nettv4u is committed to safeguarding your personal information by means of physical security.

However, there is no website that is extremely secure. Third parties may illegally intercept or access transmissions. Other users may also manipulate or misuse the information that they gathered from our website. And therefore, even though, we are working hard to protect and safeguard your privacy, we do not guarantee that all the information you transmit within our website will remain private. But we can warrant that if Nettv4u learn any breach in our security systems, we will notify you so you can make the necessary steps.

## Policy with regards to children:

Nettv4u was not ordained to children under the age of 13. We do not allow children under 13, especially without parental consent to use our website since it may contain materials that are not suitable for their age. We do not intentionally collect any information from children under 13 or eloquently allow children to use any of our services. If you know any information or children under 13 using our service, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#53002623233c2127131d3627272567267d303c3e).

## Contact:

If you have any questions and suggestions about the Nettv4u Privacy Policy Statement, please send us an email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#24775154544b5650646a4150505210510a474b49).

## Amendment to Nettv4u Privacy Policy Statement:

By using the Nettv4u website, you acknowledge your agreement to our terms stated in this Privacy Policy Statement. It is our sole discretion, to modify, amend, or update this Privacy Policy Statement any time. We will definitely notify our users regarding any changes by posting an announcement or a notice on our website. Your continued use of our service or website after the posting of any changes to our policy means you knowingly agreed to such changes. Be sure to review our Privacy Policy Statement from time to time to ensure that you will be familiar with the latest changes or any amendment made by Nettv4u. We will update the “Last Revised Date Section” at the bottom of this page when any changes were made.

## Last Revised Date of the Privacy Policy Statement:

This Privacy Policy was initially published and made effective on September 1, 2014.

#### Copyright © 2014 Nettv4u. All rights reserved. Designed by Nettv4u
